# Maria Catherine Mori

# Junior Front-End Developer

© +81-70-8362-5724

@mcm-portfolio.vercel.app

@ linkedin.com/in/maria-catherine-mori-1729b7227

@ github.com/mcm313 i Tokyo-to Koto-ku Ojima, JP

### **SUMMARY**

Dependable and self-motivated professional with ten years experience in a high-pressure office environment, seeking to start a career as a full-time developer. Software developer with a proficiency in Front-end development. Hoping to combine my business oriented skills, technical knowledge and attention to detail to provide an exciting and easy-to-use app experience for users.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Junior Front End Developer

Codebility

■2024 - Ongoing Remote

Codebility is a start-up company that aids aspiring developers to strive and achieve their goals in the IT industry.

- Responsible for coding user-side applications
- Collaborates with other team members and tracks changes in codebases.
- Builds reusable code for future use. Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.

.....

#### Cook

McDonald's

■2022 - Ongoing † Tokyo-to Koto-ku, JP

Responsible for preparing meals during breakfast, lunch, and dinner rush hours. They follow recipes with great attention to detail and apply food safety principles.

#### Financial Accountant

JPMorgan Chase Co.

■2010 - 2018 † Bonifacio Global City, Taguig City, PH

Responsible for providing timely and accurate reporting to our clients for the funds which contain a wide mix of asset types. Also for reviewing all the data for the processing and reporting of the transactions from the investors.

- Became a Subject Matter Expert (SME) for Capital Interfunding Processing and has provided training for the months May-June 2014 to support a business balancing initiative.
- Became the POC for training and development for both Capital Interfunding Processing Team and Registry Team.
- Became a Subject Matter Expert (SME) for the Xceptor project and has provided training for the new employees taking on the project.

## **EDUCATION**

Japanese Language Graduate Intercultural Institute of Japan

2018 - 2019 <sup>↑</sup> Taito-ku, Tokyo, Jp

Postgraduate Diploma in Computer Science De La Salle University

2013 - 2014 <sup>†</sup> Vito Cruz, Manila, PH

B.S. Business Administration University of Santo Tomas

2005- 2009 <sup>°</sup> Espana, Manila, PH

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Native 

Japanese Intermediate

## **STRENGTHS**

Eager to learn new skills Given that the industry is always evolving, I am constantly seeking for new ways to grow and expand my skill sets.

\_\_\_\_\_

☆ Detail-Oriented

Committed to precision in design implementation.

\_\_\_\_\_\_

Time Management

I always plan my workload so that I can meet deadlines.

\_\_\_\_\_\_

☐ Collaborative

I love to share my ideas and learnings to other team members and I believe that working with a team would make the result less prone to error and be the best it can be.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML • CSS • SCSS • JavaScript • Typescript •

React - NextJS - React Router V6 - Material UI -

Tailwind • Front End Development • GIT/Github

## **PASSIONS**

\* Technology Exploration Passionate about exploring and mastering emerging tech trends.

\_\_\_\_\_

• Coding Challenges

Love solving complex problems and challenges through coding.

**♡** Gaming

I love RPG games that use the mind and simulation games that involve planning to achieve a certain end result.